Alexander, Gabriel Arbitration Files 5133
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 72-13, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 73-9, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 73-16, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 73-11, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 73-17, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1212, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America and United Steelworkers of America, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1212, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1212, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1212, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 2194, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 2194, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 2194, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Crucible Steel Co. of America (Spaulding Works) -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1339, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Interlake Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Interlake Steel Corporation -and- USWA AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Interlake Steel Corporation -and- USWA AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Interlake Steel Corporation -and- USWA AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Interlake Steel Corporation -and- USWA AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland.) United Packinghouse Workers, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland.) United Packinghouse Workers, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland.) United Packinghouse Workers, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Swift and Co. (Springfield, Mo.) AMC and BW of NA (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Swift and Co. (Gainesville, Ga.) AMC and BW of NA, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Swift and Co. (Dexter, Mo.) AMC and BW (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Swift and Co. (St. Paul) UPWA (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Swift and Co. (St. Paul) UPWA, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland) UPWA, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland) UPWA, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Swift and Co. (Cleveland) UPWA, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Swift and Co. (Kearny, N.J.) - UPWA, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Swift and Co. (St. Louis) NBPW, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Swift and Co. (Kansas City) NBPW, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Swift and Co. (Kansas City) NBPW, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Swift and Co. (Kansas City) NBPW, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Swift and Co. (St. Louis), 1961 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Swift and Co. (Newark) - IBTCWH, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Swift and Co. (Bartow, Fla.)- ICW, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Swift and Co. (IBT), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Swift and Co. (Pittsburgh) AMCBW, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Swift and Co. (Pittsburgh) AMCBW, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Swift and Co. Local P-1170 AMCBW, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Swift and Co. -Amalgamated Mt. Cutters, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Swift and Co. (St. Louis) NBPW, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Swift and Co. (Keokuk, Iowa) AMCBWNA, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Swift and Co. (Mobile) UPFAW, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) UPFAW, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Swift and Co. AMC and BW of NA, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) NBPW, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Swift and Co. (Montgomery, Ala.) AMCBW, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Swift and Co. (E. St. Louis) and AMCBW, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- United Auto Workers and OPEI Union, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Sal. Emp. Assn. (South Works), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- U.S. Steel Corp. -Int. Union, UPGWA, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Whirlpool Corp. - Local 1918, IAM-AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Whirlpool corp. - IAM,AFL-CIO (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Whirlpool Corp. UAW Local 1172, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Whirlpool Corp. Local 174, UAW-CIO, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- The National Cash Register and NCR Employees Ind. Union, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- National Cash Register - IBEW Local 1854, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- National Motor Castings UAW-AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- North American Extrusions Corp. and Modu-Wall, Inc. - USW -AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- North American Extrusions Corp. and Modu-Wall, Inc. - USW -AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- North American Extrusions Corp. and Modu-Wall, Inc. - USW -AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- North American Extrusions Corp. and Modu-Wall, Inc. - USW -AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Naph-Sol Refining Co. OC and AW Union, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Gre-Ida Foods AMC and BW of NA, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Peerless Pattern Works and PMA of DV, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge Copper and Products Corp. Int. Union of ER and MW Local 963, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Rex Chainbelt, Inc. -USW Local 1527, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Ross Operating Valve - Local 985, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Ross Operating Valve - Local 985, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Rowe Int. Inc. IUE Local 981, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Saginaw News and Valley City Type. Union No. 50, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Appalachian Power Co. - Central Operation Co. (Philip Sporn Plant) Utility Workers AFL-CIO, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Alpena General Hosp. and United Stone and Allied - Pro. Local 206, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Addison Products Co. -UAW Local 1141, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- American Air Lines - UAW Local 1346, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Allied Painting and Decorating and Bro. of Painters, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Babcock and Wilcox Company - I.B.B., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Blaw-Knox Co. - USWA Local 1305, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Blaw-Knox Co. - USWA Local 1305, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Bloomfield Twp. Police Dept.. And AFSCME - Local 1445, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Boeing Co., Vertol Div. and UPGWA, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Bridgeport Brass Co. - Reactive Metals Products - Local 2155 USW, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Bryant Mfg. Co. - United Steelworkers, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Borden, Inc. - Local 386 R.W.D.S.U., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Calumet and Hecla, Inc. USWA Local 34312, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Cyclops Corp. - USWA, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Bucyrus-Erie Co. - USWA, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Detroit Free Press-Newspaper Guild, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- I.M.A. Association -and- R.W.A. Union, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- International Milling Co. Inc. -and- AFGM, AFL-CIO, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- International Milling Co. Inc. -and- AFGM, AFL-CIO, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- International Milling Co. Inc. and AFGM, AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Interstate United Vending Co. and United Catering Union, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Joslyn Stainless Steel -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Joslyn Stainless Steel -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Joslyn Stainless Steel -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Joslyn Stainless Steel -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Kearney and Trecker Corp. -Emp. Ind. Union, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Kearney and Trecker Corp. -Emp. Ind. Union, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Laclede Steel Co. -USWA, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Michigan Limestone Div. USS-USAPW, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Michigan Limestone Div. -UMWA, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Michigan Limestone Div. -UMWA, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Michigan Tanning and Extract Co. and AIWA, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Monsanto Company - Int. Bro. of Teamsters, CW and H of America, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Monsanto Research Corp. - UPGWA, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Diamond Reo Truck Div. - UAWA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- ALPO-Eastern Air Lines -and- Gr. Of Dent and Pereira, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Edgewater Steel Company - USSA, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Electro-Voice - I.R.E. -AFL-CIO, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Gallmeyer and Livingston - Local 19 UAW, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Hastings Mfg. Co. UAW, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Hastings Mfg. Co. -UAW, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Hasting Mfg. Co. - UAW, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Hastings Mfg. Co. -UAW, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Hydreco Unit of General Signal Corp. IAM-AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Hydreco Unit of General Signal Corp. IAM-AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Hydreco Unit of General Signal Corp. IAM-AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 22)